Peter Wexler papers 1965 - ongoing
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Papers., Series:I
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Jaffe Incoming Correspondence. 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 14-15)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - MSI Incoming Correspondence. 1990 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Lord Day Lord Incoming Correspondence. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Rehearsal Set-up Correspondence. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Bash Incoming Correspondence. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - FTL Incoming Corrrespondence. 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - QMF Incoming Correspondence. 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Credit Acknowledgement Drafts. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Credit Acknowledgement Forms. Final. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - FTL Press Release. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - QMF Transit Insurance Debate. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - QMF Registration Title, Etc. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Business Card for A. Ashenden. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Budget Review. 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 28-29)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Budget. 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Outgoing Correspondence. 1990 (Box 70, Folder 31-33)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Outgoing Correspondence. 1990 (Box 70, Folder 34-35)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Budget Tracking Vendors - Book C. 1989-1991 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Theaters. Blueprints. undated (Box 71)
  - Theatres. Blueprints. undated (Box 72)
  - SYDA II - Memorandum. 1988 (Box 73)
  - SYDA II - Business. 1988 (Box 73)
  - SYDA Foundation. Guru Mayi Birthday Celebration - Schedules and Calenders. 1988 (Box 73)
  - SYDA Foundation. Guru Mayi Birthday Celebration - Memorandum and Contact list. 1988 (Box 73)
  - SYDA Foundation. Guru Mayi Birthday Celebration - Budget. 1988 (Box 73)
  - SYDA Foundation. Guru Mayi Birthday Celebration - Programming. 1988 (Box 73)
  - SYDA Foundation. Guru Mayi Birthday Celebration - Structure Design. 1988 (Box 73)
  - SYDA Foundation. Guru Mayi Birthday Celebration - Lighting. Sound. Projections. 1988 (Box 73)
  - SYDA Foundation. Guru Mayi Birthday Celebration - Background. Includes Photographs. 1988 (Box 73)
  - Broadway Exhibit. Museum of the City of New York. Rejected proposal. 1987 (Box 73)
  - Newark Arts Center. Rejected Proposal. 1987 (Box 73)
  - Pennsylvania Ave. Development Corporation Building Exhibition. Arts Walk. Rejected Proposal. 1987 (Box 73)
  - United States Holocaust Memorial Museum. Rejected Proposal. 1987 (Box 73)
  - Aaron Shapiro. Office Door - Memorandum and Transmittals. 1987 (Box 73)
  - Aaron Shapiro. Office Door - Research. 1987 (Box 73)
  - Aaron Shapiro. Office Door - Barnard College Centenial. Rejected Proposal. 1989 (Box 73)
  - Aaron Shapiro. Office Door - Albany Urban Cultural Park. Rejected Proposal. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Contact List. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Proposal. Memorandum. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Transmittals. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Meeting Notes. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Memoranda. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Business. 1 of 2. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Press and Publicity. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Research. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Research. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Research Outtakes. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Photos. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Work Plan. Schedule. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Flag Stick Pins. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Schematics Rough. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Exhibit Images. Prior Rough Sketches. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Brochure Copy. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Exhibit Images. Photographs and frames. For Book II. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Tour Routes and Itinerary. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Budget. Technical Bids. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - General Drafts. Prior. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Photo: Research. Line: Reception, Admission. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Photo: Research. Area I: Threshold. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Photo: Research. Mobilization. 1989 (Box 73)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Photo Research. Area III. The World at War. Photocopies. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Photo Research. Area IV. The Rally. Photocopies. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Photo Research. Area V. Stress and Strains. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Photo Research. Area VI. Legacies. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book I - Proof Copy. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book I - Draft. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book I - Work Copy. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book I - As Submitted Copy. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book I - Camera Ready Art. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Scripts. Previous drafts. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book II - Draft. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book II - Camera Ready Art. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book II - Work Copy. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Book II - As Submitted Copy. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Typeface. Originals. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Original Art for Notebooks. 1989 (Box 74)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II - Sample of Preview Presentation Package. 1989 (Box 74)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League. Management Fellowship. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Baruch College. Business. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Opera Now. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Memoranda. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra - Press and Public Relations. Includes audio-cassette, Soviet Space. 1989 (Box 74)
  - TV America. The Big Deal - Contact lists. 1989 (Box 74)
  - TV America. The Big Deal - Transmitals. 1989 (Box 74)
  - TV America. The Big Deal - Business. 1989 (Box 74)
  - TV America. The Big Deal - Contracts. 1989 (Box 74)
  - TV America. The Big Deal - Background. 1989 (Box 74)
  - TV America. The Big Deal - Design as Submitted. 1989 (Box 74)
  - TV America. The Big Deal - Demonstration Version. 1989 (Box 74)
  - TV America. The Big Deal - Graphics. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Junior League. Stanford. Norwalk. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Cardinal O'Connor - Contact List. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Cardinal O'Connor - Memoranda. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Cardinal O'Connor - Transmittals. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Cardinal O'Connor - Contract. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Cardinal O'Connor - Research. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Cardinal O'Connor - Design as Submitted. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Cardinal O'Connor - Props. 1989 (Box 74)
  - Photo Illusions - Contact sheet. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Photo Illusions - Transmittals. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Photo Illusions - Correspondence. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Photo Illusions - Art Work. 1990 (Box 75)
  - MSCI. Institute for International Scientific Cooperation. Correspondence. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Search for Life. Tour. Memorandum. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Development Company - Renderings. Transmittals. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Development Company - Convention. Transmittals. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Development Company - Convention. Memoranda. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Development Company - Convention Booth. Includes photographs. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Research. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Business. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Memoranda. 1990 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Development. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Contact Lists. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Transmittals. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Memorandum. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Press and Public Relations. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Design as Submitted. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Oxford Realty - Background. Includes photographs and slides. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Cooperative State Research Service - Memorandum. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Cooperative State Research Service - Meeting Notes. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Cooperative State Research Service - Business. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Cooperative State Research Service - Research. 1989 (Box 75)
  - John F. Fulkerson. Letters regarding death. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Library of Congress. Ties and attachments. Italian Americans in the West. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Library of Congress. Two Proposals for Treasures of the Vatican. 1989 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Contact Sheet. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Contracts. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Transmittals. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Memorandum. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Matty Powers Estimates. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Furniture Research. Catalogues. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Research. Interiors. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Printer Research. Material. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Matthews Company - Printers. Estimates and Samples. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Equitable. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers. Gala - Contact Sheet. Lobby. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Equitable. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers. Gala - Contract. Lobby. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Equitable. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers. Gala - Correspondence. Lobby. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Equitable. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers. Gala - Balloon. Bouquets. Lobby. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Equitable. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers. Gala - Schedules and Floor plans. Lobby. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Equitable. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers. Gala - Business. Insurance. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Equitable. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers. Gala - Research. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Equitable. Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers. Gala - Mr. Abbott Program and Book. 1991 (Box 75)
  - Toys for Tots. Contract. Letter of Agreement. 1991 (Box 75)
  - N. Glantz and Son. Exhibit Booth - Contact sheet. 1991 (Box 76)
  - N. Glantz and Son. Exhibit Booth - Contract Drafts. 1991 (Box 76)
  - N. Glantz and Son. Exhibit Booth - Design Development. 1991 (Box 76)
  - N. Glantz and Son. Exhibit Booth - Research. 1991 (Box 76)
  - N. Glantz and Son. Exhibit Booth - Business. 1991 (Box 76)
  - N. Glantz and Son. Exhibit Booth - Memorandum. Includes photographs and negatives. 1991 (Box 76)
  - N. Glantz and Son. Exhibit Booth - Transmittals. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Potential Projects. Library of Congress - Proposal as Submitted. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Potential Projects. Library of Congress - Drafts. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Potential Projects. Library of Congress - Discovery Center. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Potential Projects. Library of Congress - Future Reference. 1991 (Box 76)
  - American Symphony Orchestra - League Management. Letters from Judith Kurz regarding Fellows meeting. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Potential Projects. Library of Congress - Sound and Light. Mailing letters. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Sound and Light - Business. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Sound and Light - Correspondence. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Sound and Light - Transmittals. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Sound and Light - Jaffe Journalist Mailing List. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Sound and Light - Memorandum. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York Philharmonic. Fan Project. Letter. Photo in Life Magazine. 1993 (Box 76)
  - Sedona. 1993 (Box 76)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League. 1993 (Box 76)
  - Budapest. 1993 (Box 76)
  - African Portraits. 1993 (Box 76)
  - Mexico - Transmittals. 1992 (Box 76)
  - Mexico - Correspondence. 1992 (Box 76)
  - New York Philharmonic. Fan Project. 1992 (Box 76)
  - New York Philharmonic. Education Project - Transmittals. 1992 (Box 76)
  - New York Philharmonic. Education Project - Draft Proposals. 1992 (Box 76)
  - Lincoln Center. Midsummer Nights Swing - Transmittals. 1992 (Box 76)
  - Lincoln Center. Midsummer Nights Swing - Notes. 1992 (Box 76)
  - Lincoln Center. Midsummer Nights Swing - Preliminary Drawings. 1992 (Box 76)
  - Lincoln Center. Midsummer Nights Swing - Existing Site Plans. 1992 (Box 76)
  - ATMA. Music Movement Image. Business. 1992 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Festival - Contact Sheet. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Festival - Memorandum. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Festival - Transmittals. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Festival - Business. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Festival - Options 1, 2, 3. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Festival - Press Clippings. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Sculpture - Memorandum. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Sculpture - Business. 1991 (Box 76)
  - New York City Opera. Sculpture - Research. 1991 (Box 76)
  - Library of Congress. Vatican - Drafts and Notes. 1991-1992 (Box 76)
  - Library of Congress. Vatican - Original RFP document with amendments. 1991-1992 (Box 76)
  - Library of Congress. Vatican - Sub-Contractors information. Includes audio cassette from Acoustiguide. 1991-1992 (Box 76)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Contact Sheets. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Contracts. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Transmittals. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Memoranda. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Meeting Notes and Materials. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Report Pieces. Budget Draft. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Report Pieces. Budget Draft. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Report Pieces. First Draft of Budget. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Business Proposals. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Drafts of NSO business proposals. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Draft Reports. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Report Pieces. The Movies. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Report Tracking. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Executive Summary. A. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Report Complete. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Executive Summary. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Executive Summary Report. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Report. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Report Pieces. Proposals. 1 September 1996 A. Extra Charts. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Business. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Marketing. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Markets. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Music for Words. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Background Research. Includes floppy disk. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. America Hoorah. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Star Spangled Banner. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Ken Burns. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Cinema. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. NSO. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Internet. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Companies. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. CD ROMs. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Newspaper Stories. 1996 (Box 77)
  - National Symphony Orchestra. Music in America - Research. Leonard Bernstein. 1996 (Box 77)
  - Eldridge Street Project. 1996 (Box 78)
  - AVI Prudential Security. Correspondence. 1996 (Box 78)
  - AT and T Correspondence, Rough Proposals, and Final Proposals. 1996 (Box 78)
  - Buddy Holly. 1996 (Box 78)
  - Who's Who in America. 1995 (Box 78)
  - Studio Christmas Cards. 1995 (Box 78)
  - ASOL Correspondence. 1995 (Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1995 (Box 78)
  - TCI Theatre Architecture. 1995 (Box 78)
  - Horatio Alger Award. Correspondence, Video Tapes, Promotional Documents. 1995 (Box 78)
  - American Anthem/LTV Center Media Exhibition of Sounds and Symbols of American History. Trammel Crow Company, Dallas, TX. 1985 (Box 78)
  - American Anthem/LTV Center Media Exhibition of Sounds and Symbols of American History. Film Cassettes Produced Material. 1985 (Box 78)
  - American Anthem/LTV Center Media Exhibition of Sounds and Symbols of American History. VHS Cassettes Produced Material and Press Release. 1985 (Box 78)
  - American Anthem/LTV Center Media Exhibition of Sounds and Symbols of American History. Beta Cassette Produced Material. 1985 (Box 78)
  - American Anthem/LTV Center Media Exhibition of Sounds and Symbols of American History. Single Track Reel to Reel Audio Track Masters. 1985 (Box 78)
  - Calgary. 1997 (Box 79)
  - Calgary Center. 1996 (Box 79)
  - DFW. 1996 (Box 79)
  - Who's Who in America. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Various Articles, etc. of interest. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Julian Poole The Fund for Arts and Culture In Central and Eastern Europe. 1994 (Box 79)
  - American Symphony Orchestra league. 1994 (Box 79)
  - New Jersey Symphony Orchestra. 1994 (Box 79)
  - St. John the Divine. Donor Recognition. 1994 (Box 79)
  - St. John the Divine. Contact Sheet. 1994 (Box 79)
  - St. John the Divine. Contracts. 1994 (Box 79)
  - St. John the Divine. Transmittals. 1994 (Box 79)
  - St. John the Divine. Memoranda. 1994 (Box 79)
  - St. John the Divine. Schedules. 1994 (Box 79)
  - St. John the Divine. Press and Public Relations. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Ninth Avenue Bridges - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Transmittals. 1995 (Box 79)
  - Ninth Avenue Bridges - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Correspondence. 1995 (Box 79)
  - Ninth Avenue Bridges - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Design Background. 1995 (Box 79)
  - Ninth Avenue Bridges - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Press and Public Relations. 1995 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Contact Sheets. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Contracts. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Transmittals. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Press and Public Relations. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Correspondence. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Schedules. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Menus. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Item Lists. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Pricing. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Bid Lists. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Vendors. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Manganaro's Hero Boy. Photos. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Spring Creek Festival '94. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Spring Creek Festival '94. Correspondence. 1994 (Box 79)
  - Spring Creek Festival '94. Newspaper Articles. 1994 (Box 79)
  - New York City Transit Authority. 1991 (Box 79)
  - New York City Transit Authority. Proposal. 1991 (Box 79)
  - New York City Transit Authority. Final Proposal as submitted. 1991 (Box 79)
  - Jaffe Acoustics - General Company Information. 1991 (Box 79)
  - New York City Transit Authority. Preliminary notes and drafts. 1991 (Box 79)
  - New York City Transit Authority. MSI information - general. 1991 (Box 79)
  - Potential Project: New York City Transit Authority RFP-CM 831. 1991 (Box 79)
  - The Search for Life - United Stated Dept. of Agriculture. Exhibition Smithsonian. 1987 (Box 80)
  - Museum of American History. Slides for 3-Screen Show Binders. 1987 (Box 80)
  - Museum of American History. Film Cassettes Promational Tapes. 1987 (Box 80)
  - Museum of American History. VHS Cassettes Research Tapes. 1987 (Box 80)
  - The Search for Life - United States Dept. of Agriculture. Exhibition Smithsonian. 1987 (Box 81)
  - National Museum of American History. Matrix Created Source - Dub off of VHS. 1987 (Box 81)
  - National Museum of American History. Source Tape - Bender Tape of Show. 1987 (Box 81)
  - National Museum of American History. Unrevised Edit Master - Outside Reel A and B. 1987 (Box 81)
  - The Search for Life - United States Dept. of Agriculture. Exhibition Smithsonian. 1987 (Box 82)
  - National Museum of American History. Video Film Cassette Source Tapes. 1987 (Box 82)
  - The Search for Life - United States Dept. of Agriculture. Exhibition Smithsonian. 1987 (Box 83)
  - National Museum of American History. Unrevised Edited Master - Inside Reel C, D, E. 1987 (Box 83)
  - National Museum of American History. Outside Cassette A and B (Dubbing Masters and Dubs). 1987 (Box 83)
  - National Museum of American History. Inside Cassettes C, D, E (Dubbing Masters and Dubs). 1987 (Box 83)
  - The Search for Life - United States Dept. of Agriculture. Exhibition Smithsonian. 1987 (Box 84)
  - National Museum of American History. Reel to Reel Multi Track - Cold Spring Harbor. 1987 (Box 84)
  - National Museum of Americn History. Reel to Reel Multi Track - General Misc. Sound Effects, Narration. 1987 (Box 84)
  - National Museum of American History. Reel to Reel Single Track - General (Outs). 1987 (Box 84)
  - National Museum of American History. Reel to Reel Single Track - Cold Spring Harbor. 1987 (Box 84)